Finding Aid for School of Information (University of Michigan) Records 1901-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean's Files
  - Martha Pollock
    - Administrative records
      - Doctoral Program: correspondence, admission and enrollment materials, rosters 2007-2010
      - Emergency Information and Plans circa 2008
      - Enrollment Information 2008-2009
      - Executive Education: correspondence, planning materials, sample curricula 2008-2009
      - External Advisory Board (meeting materials, minutes, and rosters) 2007-2010
      - Faculty (correspondence, memoranda, projects, etc.) 2007-2010
      - Health Informatics (program proposals and planning materials) 2008-2010
      - History: records of the School of Information's involvement with various groups and initiatives as well as documentation of personnel issues; includes files from previous Deans John L. King and Olivia Frost 2004-2010
      - Informatics Program (Undergraduate Degree Program) 2007-2010
      - International Programs (Letters of Intent, Memoranda of understanding, and correspondence) 2005-2009
      - John Seely Brown Symposium 2008
      - JSTOR (service agreements and information about relationship to the School of Information) 2004-2009
      - Libraries (correspondence, reports, meeting materials related to evolution of librarianship) 2007-2009
      - Management Team circa 2007
      - Meeting Notes: faculty, students, administrators 2007-2010
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2080 ]
      - Mentoring (faculty), 2011Merit Review (Faculty Annual Reviews) 2007/2008-2010/2011
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2040 ]
      - Miscellaneous: draft correspondence, planning documents, other writings circa 2009-2010
      - MSI Program: reports, job placement data, new student materials,2006-2009
      - North Quad: planning materials 2009-2010
        - Audiovisual equipment and infrastructure
        - Budgets and Development
        - Deans' Suite
        - Floorplans and Office Assignments
        - North Quad Pictures
        - North Quad Programming
        - North Quad Schedule
        - North Quad Staff (proposals and position announcements from the North Quad Governing Committee)
        - Space Analysis
      - Open Access Information (related to various initiatives and issues) 2007-2008
      - Policies (regarding appointments, conflict of interest, purchases, etc.) circa 2005-2007
      - Post-Deanship 2010-2011
      - Presentations 2007-2010
        (includes State of the School and commencement addresses as well as presentations to External Advisory Board, alumni groups, prospective students, etc.)
      - Rackham (correspondence, reports, and other records related to the School of Information's separation from the Rackham School of Graduate Studies) 2009-2010
      - Rankings and comparatives (surveys on academic departments prepared by the Computer Research Association) 2006-2009
      - Research Proposals (Faculty) circa 2008-2010
      - Salary (comparison of salaries among U-M deans) 2003-2009
      - Search Files 2008-2010
        (materials related to faculty searches, including interdisciplinary faculty initiative)
      - Undergraduate Concentration 2012
- Audiotapes
  The Audiotapes series is arranged alphabetically by topic and contains recordings of lectures given at the school. Included are tapes of the Alumni-in-Residence presentations and Beta Phi Mu lectures and recordings of the guest lecturers in the course L.S. 813 Trends and Issues in Librarianship.
  - Alumni-in-Residence
    - Casy, Geneviere April 7, 1973 "Alternative Futures for the Public Library", 7"; 3.75 ips reel (Box 31)
    - Darling, Richard April 6, 1973 "The Librarian and Intellectual Freedom", 1 reels 7"; 3.75 ips (Box 31)
    - Jones, Clara April 1, 1971 "The Urban Library Scene: Challenges and Changes", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
    - Miller, Marilyn March 24, 1988, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
    - Reid, David April 7, 1978, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
    - Slate, Ted March 25, 1988, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
  - Beta Phi Mu
    - October 21, 1965 Dan Fink, "Aims of Documentation", 7"; 3.75 ips reel (Box 31)
    - April 7, 1972 Honoring Edmon Low on his retirement), 1 audiocassettes 1 90 minutes (Box 31)
  - Bishop Lecture 1976
    - Churchwell, Charles, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
    - Srygley, Sara, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
  - Convocations and Lectures
    - Lecturers Undated
      - Jones, Virginia Lacy, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
      - Richardson, Selma, "Mirror/rorrim", 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes (Box 31)
    - November 2, 1972 Grace Slocum "Defining Total Community Library Service" and John Q. Bedford, "The Philadelphia Student Library Project", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
    - March 16, 1978 (Dr. H. Totten, "Minority Recruitment", 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes (Box 31)
    - October 4, 1990 James J. Duderstadt, Ehrlicher Room Dedication, 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
  - L.S. 813, Trends and Issues in Librarianship
    - 1973
      - September 11, Dr. Fredrick Wagman, "Trends and Issues in University Librarianship", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - September 18, Joshua Smith, "Trends and Issues in Information Science", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - September 25, Richard Chapin, "Networks and Bibliographic Control in Academic Libraries", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - September 28, Dr. Asheim, "Trends and Issues in Library Education", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - October 2, Selma Richardson, "Trends and Issues in School Librarianship", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - October 9, A.P. Marshall and Mary Daume, "Current Issues Facing ALA and State Library Associations", cassettes (Box 31)
      - October 16, Eileen D. Cooke "Federal Library Legislation Today and Tomorrow", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - October 23, Evan Farber, "Trends and Issues in College Librarianship", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - October 30, F. Kurt Cylke, "Trends and Issues in Federal Library Service", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - November 6, Judith Hopkins, "Trends and Issues in Technical Services", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - November 20, Judith F. Krug, "Current Issues in Intellectual Freedom", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - November 27, Allie Beth Martin, "Trends and Issues in Public Libraries", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - December 4, Joe Shubert, "Trends and Issues in the State Library", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - December 11, Robert Muller, "Faculty Status and Unionization in the Academic Library", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - December 13, Dan Lacy, "Trends and Issues in Publishing", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
    - 1977
      - January 20, Rebecca T. Bingham, "The School Library Media Center", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - February 10, E. J. Josey, "Trends and Issues in State Libraries", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - February 17, Eileen Cooke, "Libraries and Political Process", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - February 24, Lillian M. Bradshaw, "The Public Library Alternative Futures and New Directions", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 3, Forrest F. Carhart, Jr., "Library Cooperation", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 24, Estelle Brodman, "The Medical Library", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 31, Frank A. Stevens, "Federal Aid to Library Education", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - April 7, Jane G. Flener, "The University Library", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
      - April 14, Bessie Boehm Moore, "The National Commission on Libraries and Information Science", 1 audiocassettes 120 minutes (Box 31)
    - 1978
      - January 12, Ella G. Yates, "Trends and Issues in Public Libraries", 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes (Box 31)
      - February 2, Evan Farber "The College Library", 60 audiocassettes (Box 31)
      - February 23, Charles Churchwell, "The University Library", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 2, Rebecca Bingham, "The School Library Media Center", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 16, James Skipper, "University Library Cooperation", 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 23, Bessie Boehm Moore, "Planning for the White House Conference", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
      - March 30, Daniel Lacy, "Publishing Trends", 1 audiocassettes 60 minutes (Box 31)
      - April 6, Frank X. Scannell, "The State Library", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
      - April 13, Estelle Brodman, "The Medical Library", 1 audiocassettes 90 minutes (Box 31)
- Photographs, 1906-1994, 2 linear feet
  The Photographs series (2 linear feet) is divided into four subseries: Class Photographs, Events, Individuals and Topical. The Events subseries includes a mixture of prints, proof sheets, and negatives. In the other three subseries, prints predominate. Arranged chronologically, the Class Photographs subseries contains group portraits (frequently identified) of students and faculty, as well as some individual student portraits from the years 1950 to 1952. The Events subseries is arranged chronologically. It consists of prints (with individuals often identified), negatives and proof sheets from a variety of conferences, lectures, ceremonies and convocations. The Individuals subseries, arranged alphabetically by surname, includes photographs of deans, faculty members, students, and alumni. The Topical subseries includes photos of campus libraries and classroom scenes. The "Unidentified" files contain a variety of shots, mostly event candids and classroom scenes. The "Small Group" photographs are undated and uncontextualized images of faculty, students and other persons. The individuals in these small group photos have been identified for the most part.
  - Class Photographs 1909-1980s
    - 1909-1933 (Box 34)
    - 1940s (Box 34)
    - Individual portraits 1950-1952 (Box 34)
    - 1950-1953 (Box 34)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 34)
    - 1968-1980 (Box 34)
    - C.R.L. Students 1983, Undated (Box 34)
  - Events 1906-1994
    - 1906-1930 (Box 34)
    - American Library Association, Philadelphia 1955 (Box 34)
    - 1957 Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - 1950s Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Student-Faculty Luncheon May 22, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Student-Faculty Luncheon August 1, 1962 (Box 34)
    - American Library Association, New York 1966 (Box 34)
    - 1960s Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - 1970 Miscellaneous (Scrapbook) (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence 1971 (Box 34)
    - 50th Anniversary Banquet 1976 (Box 34)
    - 1977 Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence March 22, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Honorary Degree Ceremony for Virginia Jones August 18, 1979 (Box 34)
    - 1970s Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence (Ching-Chih Chen and Roger Jacobs) March 20-21, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Rose Vainstein Day May 16, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Library Science Faculty Dinner Spring 1980 (Box 34)
    - Alice Ihrig Convocation September 11, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Beta Phi Mu/Convocation December 4, 1980 (Box 34)
    - Harry Chapin and Bob Denver Visits 1980 (Box 34)
    - Technology Institute 1980 (Box 34)
    - 1980 Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Orientations 1980-1981 (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence April 2-3, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Ken Vance Convocation April 29, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Eugene Garfield Convocation May 19, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Graduation Ceremony August 13, 1981 (Box 34)
    - Peggy Sullivan Convocation October 5, 1981 (Box 34)
    - 1981 Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - William Warner Bishop Lecture 1981, 1984 (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence (Louis Martin, Duane Webster) April 1982 (Box 34)
    - 1982 Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Alumni-in-Residence (Karen Horny and John Parker) April 7-8, 1983 (Box 34)
    - 1983 Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - "Library Conversations" Program 1983-1984 (Box 34)
    - Beta Phi Mu Inductions 1983-1985 (Box 35)
    - 1984 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Russell Bidlack Retirement Dinner April 5, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Charles Churchwell Convocation October 4, 1984 (Box 35)
    - Washington D.C. Trip (Russell Bidlack) 1984 (Box 35)
    - Miriam Drake Convocation January 24, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Paul Kaegman February 14, 1985 (Box 35)
    - Alumni-in-Residence (Francis Buckley, Pauline Wilson) March 28-29, 1985 (Box 35)
    - 1985 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Awards Ceremony April 10, 1986 (Box 35)
    - 1986 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Ken Dowlin Convocation February 12, 1987 (Box 35)
    - 1987 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - 1988 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - International Federation of Library Associations, Brighton, England 1989 (Box 35)
    - 1989 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - International Federation of Library Associations, Sweden 1990 (Box 35)
    - Ehrlicher Room Dedication 1990 (Box 35)
    - 1990 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Information Symposium (Warner) 1991 (Box 35)
    - 1991-1994 Miscellaneous (Box 35)
    - Trip to Bangkok Undated (Box 35)
    - Unidentified Events, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Individuals
    - "A-B" (Box 35)
    - Bidlack, Russell (Box 35)
    - Bishop, William Warner (Box 35)
    - "C" (Box 35)
    - "D-F" (Box 35)
    - "G-K" (Box 35)
    - "L-M" (Box 35)
    - "N-S" (Box 35)
    - Warner, Robert (Box 35)
    - "T-Z" (Box 35)
  - Topical
    - Campus Buildings
      - Libraries (Box 35)
      - West Engineering Building, 1980s-1990s (Box 35)
    - Classroom Scenes 1980-1982 (Box 35)
    - Library Scenes circa 1920s-1960s (Box 35)
    - Small Groups (Identified), 4 folders (Box 35)
    - Unidentified
      - circa 1950s-1960s (Box 35)
      - circa late 1960s-1970s (Box 35)
      - circa 1980s (Box 35)
- Faculty Meetings 1927-1994
  The Faculty Meetings series (2.25 linear feet) includes meeting minutes, agendas, notes, and meeting attachments. The series is arranged two subseries. The first, covering the years 1927-1994, consists of the original binders of minutes, notes and related material. It is arranged in reverse chronological order with the meeting minutes maintained in the original office binder and the accompanying materials in folders directly behind the office binder. The binders often contain a subject index for the minutes. The series provides a complete record of the administrative activities of the faculty. This is particularly true until 1992. The record of minutes for 1993 and 1994 document only a few meetings. Overall, the record of the meetings serve to provide a brief summary of the school's announcements and news, enrollment figures and related discussion, budget, changes in faculty, committee activities, curriculum changes, discussion and voting on school policies and procedures, and research proposals.
  The second subseries, Faculty Meeting reports, 1917-1974 (.25 linear feet, accessioned in 2002) are is an addition of typewritten meeting reports and related materials that complements the main series of minutes.
  - Faculty Meeting Notes, Memos and Minutes
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1927-1964, 13 folders (Box 5)
    - Faculty Meeting Notes (mimeographs and memos relating to faculty meetings) 1956-1964 (Box 5)
    - Notes and Memos 1963-1966 (Box 37)
    - Minutes 1965-1972 (Box 37)
    - Notes and Memos 1967-1971 (Box 37)
    - Minutes 1972-1975 (Box 37)
    - Notes and Memos 1972-1974 (Box 37)
    - Minutes 1975-1979 (Box 37)
    - Notes and Memos 1975-1978 (Box 37)
    - Minutes 1979-1985 (Box 37)
    - Notes and Memos 1978-1984 (Box 37)
    - February 21, 1985-May 4, 1989 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1987-1988 (Box 38)
    - September 1989-December 1992 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1988-1989 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1989-1990 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1990-1991 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1991-1992 (Box 38)
    - Notes and Memos 1992-1993 (Box 38)
    - Minutes 1993-1994 (Box 38)
  - Minutes, etc. 1927-1969
    - 1927-1929 (Box 44)
    - 1930-1935 (Box 44)
    - 1935-1939 (Box 44)
    - 1940-1945 (Box 44)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 44)
    - 1950-1955 (Box 44)
    - 1960-1965 (Box 44)
    - 1966-1969 (Box 44)
    - Faculty Policies 1969-1974 (Box 44)
- Course Material 1926-1995
  The Course Materials series (3 linear feet) is comprised of documentation of discontinued courses offered within the Library Science Department (L.S.) and within the School of Information and Library Studies (I.L.S.). The record of discontinued courses date from 1926 to the 1994-1995 school year. The office procedure was to establish a folder for each course in the school's record keeping system. Each course folder contains a wealth of information. Documentation on the courses may include a copy of the official record of course change (Office of Registration received the original), course description, instructor, course syllabi, examination questions, course assignments, and student reports. Student reports are found mainly for those courses taught in the Library Science Department. The series will be immensely useful for a researcher interested in studying the change in the school's curriculum from one focused on book cataloging and library management to one centered on information management within a wide variety of environments and institutions. The Course Materials are divided into two subseries, 1926-1965 and 1935-1995, reflecting the manner in which the files were received.
  - 1926-1965
    - L.S. 103, Cataloging and Classification 1932-1947, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - L.S. 104, Cataloging and Classification 1926-1933 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 109, Book Selection 1933 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 110, Book Selection 1946-1948 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 111, Library Administration 1930-1948 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 112, Library Administration 1927-1948 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 113 (taught by Joeckel) 1927-1928 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 114 Summer 1927 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 115, High School Library 1927 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 119, Reference Work 1930-1948, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - L.S. 120, Reference Work and Bibliography 1945-1948 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 121, School Library Work 1930-1932 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 126, Special Collections II 1926-1927 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 127, History of Books and Printing undated (Box 3)
    - L.S. 128, The Making of a Book undated (Box 3)
    - L.S. 134, Special Libraries and Special Collections undated (Box 3)
    - L.S. 135, Periodicals and Serials 1945-1947 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 141, Technical Processes 1947 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 1943, 1947, 1957 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 144, Historical Manuscripts 1942 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 148, Library Materials in High School 1947 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 151, History of Children's Literature undated (Box 3)
    - L.S. 156, Library Work with Children 1947 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 158, School Library Administration 1947 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 201, Advanced Reference and Bibliography 1938-1939 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 203, Lectures by Miss Warren (includes detailed lecture outlines) 1949-1950 (Box 3)
    - L.S. 204, Library Administration (includes detailed lecture outlines) 1949-1959, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - L.S. 206 1936-1937 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 209, Seminar on University Library Administration (taught by Bishop) 1927-1941, 14 folders (Box 4)
    - L.S. 210, Seminar 1938 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 211, Book Selection 1948-1950 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 219, General Reference Materials and Bibliography of the Humanities 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 230, Classification Problems 1937 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 271, The School Library and the School Program 1938, 1943 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 273, School Library Work for Teacher Librarians 1938 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 278, Public Library Administration 1956 (Box 4)
    - L.S. 309, Seminar 1940-1942, 1950, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - L.S. 342, Library Buildings 1942 (Box 4)
    - Legislative Reference undated (Box 4)
    - Library Science for Educators 1947 (Box 4)
    - New York State Library School, course materials 1904 (Box 4)
    - Public Libraries 1956 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous course material 1940-1963 (Box 4)
  - 1935-1995
    - L.S. 514, Library Administration 1960s (Box 12)
      (seminar involving guest lectures by leaders in library science)
    - L.S. 813, Trends and Issues 1973-1979, 7 folders (Box 12)
    - L.S. 861, Seminar in Library Education Fall 1979 (Box 12)
    - L.S. 301 Advanced Studies in Reference and Bibliography (Box 41)
    - L.S. 310 1945 (Box 41)
    - L.S. 321/322 1935-1943 (Box 41)
    - L.S. Bibliography of American History and Literature 1957 (Box 41)
    - L.S. Workshop on Library Buildings 1957 (Box 41)
    - L.S. 385/386 Seminar in Public Library Administration (Box 41)
    - L.S. 401 Introduction to Bibliography (Box 41)
    - L.S. 431 Organization of Materials in the School Library (Box 41)
    - L.S. 442 Curriculum Materials in the School Library (Box 41)
    - L.S. 493 and 495 Summer Institute 1968 (Box 41)
    - L.S. 500 The Information Profession (Box 41)
    - L.S. 513 The Library as a Public Service Institution (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 520 Information Resources: Production, Distribution, and Evaluation (Box 41)
    - L.S. 522 Evaluation and Development of the Book Collection (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 523 (Frost) Organization of Information Resources (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 523 (Drabenstott) Organization of Information Resources (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 523 (Warner) Organization of Information Resources (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 526 (Janes) Technologies for Information Management (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 526 (Mason) Technologies for Information Management (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 526 (Rosenberg) Technologies for Information Management (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 526, (Warner) Technologies for Information Management (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 529 Sources of General Information (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 530 (Drabenstott) Searching Automated Databases (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 530 (Janes) Searching Automated Databases (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 530 (Mackintosh) Searching Automated Databases (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 545 (Avrin) History of Books and Printing 1988-1993 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 545 (Slavens) History of Books and Printing (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 552 Publishing 1991-1994 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 556 Media Production (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 558 Photographic Communication (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 560 Reading Interests of Adults (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 565 (Beaver) Literature for Children (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 565 (Taylor) Literature for Children (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 575 (Ed.D575) Teaching Role of the School Library Media Specialist (Box 41)
    - L.S. 576 Administration of the School Library Media Program 1950-1983 (Box 41)
    - L.S. 580 Federal Government Information Sources (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 600 (HST 600) Introduction to Archives and Records Management (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 601 Concepts of Information Retrieval (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 603 Image Databases 1995 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 603 Special Topics in Academic Libraries (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 603 Video Communication 1995 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 605 (IPPS 728) Graduate Seminar: Ethics and Values Dilemmas in Use of Information Technology: Policy Implications for Institutions of Higher Learning 1994 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 606 Internet: Resource Discovery and Organization 1993 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 607 The Information Industry/The Business of Information 1995 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 607 Information Technology, Impacts, and Implications 1992 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 607 Instruction to Academic and Research Libraries 1991 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 608 Special Topics: International Librarianship 1992 (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 608 Special Topics: Organization of Networked and Digital Information (Box 41)
    - I.L.S. 613 Human Computer Interaction Software Projects Lab 1995 (Box 42)
    - I.L.S. 620 Collection Development and Management 1991-1995 (Box 42)
    - I.L.S. 623 Organization of Information Resources II (Box 42)
    - I.L.S. 626 Description and Access Systems for Non-Verbal Information Resources (Box 42)